Worth living for. Worth dying for.
Warhorse One is a action, war, drama film directed by Johnny Strong.
A gunned down Navy SEAL Master Chief must guide a child to safety through a gauntlet of
hostile Taliban insurgents and survive the brutal Afghanistan wilderness.
Master Chief Richard Mirko, played by Johnny Strong.
Zoe Walters, played by Athena Durner.
Radam, played by Raj Kala.
Petty Officer James 'G' Wiliker, played by James Sherrill.
Tarad, played by Siya Rostami.
Jarrah, played by Danny Augustus.
Warhorse One is a 2023 American war action drama film directed by and written by William Kaufman and Johnny Strong
(directorial debut), starring Strong and Athena Durner; Kaufman and Strong also had other roles.
The film tells the story of a Navy SEAL Master Chief who
accidentally lands in the mountains on the Afghan border.
He must lead a child in distress to safety before air support
arrives, fighting Taliban rebels along the way.
The film was released in limited release in the United States on June
30, 2023, and on VOD and digitally on July 4, 2023.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of afghanistan, rescue mission,
afghanistan war (2001-2021), taliban, u.s. navy seal.
The tone is dark and emotional.